pwinsider.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy | PWInsider.com

**Privacy Policy**

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated by this web site, (including any sub-site accessible through the homepage, the "Site"). This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

PWInsider.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to this Site. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or email address, is automatically collected from visitors to this Site. Personally identifiable information about visitors to this Site is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted by you. We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of this Site. In those instances when we do collect personally identifiable information, PWInsider.com will notify you when we are collecting personally identifiable information about you. 

Personally identifiable information that visitors submit to this Site is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we disclose other uses in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. However, at the time of collection, you will have the option of instructing us not to send you additional information or share your personal information with third parties. PWInsider.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of our advertisers or business partners. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**IP Tracking**  
Please note that we have a feature enabled that will allow us to deny the ability to view the page to specific IP addresses. This feature is enabled due to so many websites copying and pasting our work, stealing it and passing it off as their own. If we can get the IP address of someone who we know steals our work, we can then block that person from being able to read the site. It started due to a person named Bixenspan. Unfortunately, there are some seriously deranged wrestling fans out there. Please note that IP addresses are not collected or stored by PWInsider.com.

Partner of USA Today Sports Media.
